Leopoldo Ortega Jr

My Portfolio: https://leovportfolio.netlify.app/
(320)298-5260 • leopoldoortegav@gmail.com

Professional Summary

I am a hard worker who has worked in various industries across the world. I have been learning front-end web technologies for quite some time and I am looking forward to expanding my knowledge and to become a member of your team.

Skills and Technologies

Machinery operation

• Web Development

• Bilingual (English & Spanish)

HTML & CSS

• git & github

• javaScript

SASS

PugJS

NodeJS

ReactJS

Linux OS

• Reliable, motivated and quick learner

Work History

Machine Operator/Sunopta/Alexandria, MN/Oct 2020 - present

- Operated warehouse equipment and reported instances of safety code violations to management to reduce risk of accidents.
- Operated an HMI (Human Machine Interface) computer and ensured that all production operation flows without error.
- Operated a forklift to move supplies around warehouse and production.
- Handled dangerous chemicals and followed all safety protocol.
- Member of company safety committee to ensure that workplace is safe and free of hazards.

Production operator/ Mocopinus / Karlsruhe, GERMANY / September 2019 – July 2020

- Packaged finished timber/wood products and prepared packages for accurate shipping.
- Used established assembly instructions to complete jobs quickly, accurately and with zero errors.
- Supported machine operators in setup and operation of production equipment resulting in efficient runs.
- Great communication and teamwork in an international workplace.

Production worker / Mercedes-Benz / Woerth, GERMANY / April 2019- September 2019

- Inspected final products to assess compliance with quality standards and established tolerances.
- Examined incoming materials and compared to documentation for accuracy and quality.
- Documented production information via daily system logs and discussed non-conformance issues with management.
- Adapted quickly to a German-speaking work environment.

Education

High School Diploma / *Kingsburg, CA* / *June 2013* - Kingsburg High School **Fresno State University** / *Aug 2013* - *May 2015*